	Driver View											
												
												
	Driver ID	First Name	Phone	Email	LicenseType							
												
												
												
												
B	"Driver ID can also be the. I don't know the data field, the record ID or whatever you use to identify. The record It does not necessarily need to be displayed in the data view. It's just a way to keep track of that record, if that makes any sense. "											
C	First name is exactly what it is. It's the first name of the driver. 											
D	"Again, the last name of the driver now. I have separate fields here for first name and last name, but how can we when we display it on the data grid view? Just show those combined into first name, last name format. I will let you decide how to do that, because I am a novice programmer. "											
F	"There are two license types in my fleet. There is a cdl license, and there is a passenger license. This needs to be a drop down so we can change that. It doesn't. necessarily have any other function than to identify the driver so that it doesn't need to have any other function inside of bus bus, other than to identify the driver has a CDL or a passenger license. "											
G	"Again, we need to provide driver view the proper instructions to format the shared dynamic. Data grid on. The content panel of the dashboard view. So when the button on the side panel pressing driver it will implement the instructions to change the view in the dynamic data grid to match the formatting and function of these fields. "											
												
