	Primary Key	Date	Route Name	Bus	AM Begin Mileage	AM End Mileage	AM Riders	AM Driver	PM Start Mileage	PM End Mileage	PM Riders	PM Driver
												
		"I am not exactly sure how to approach this. But each day we'll have four different routes. The Truck Plaza route, The East Route, The West Route and the SPED Route"										
		"So in my vision, each scheduled school day will have these four routes. So based on how you think we should implement it, what I envision is. And maybe this is not even the appropriate route way to do it, but each. each scheduled school day will have a grouping of these four routes that I will put in the mileage, the driver, the bus and I'll manually enter in the AM begin mileage am end mileage AM riders PM start mileage PM end mileage PM writers and PM drivers if that makes sense. I think on the data grid view when we're entering data. If we group those together. we can keep them organized. I am a novice programmer. I will leave it up to you on how to implement that. But let me know how you do it and make it clear in the route view how that works. "										
		"B) For Date, use Date picker function and format the display to read DD-MM-YY in the field"										
		"C) There are 4 routes that operate on any given school day. Truck Plaza is assigned Bus 17, but can change due o maintenance or other factors.  This will be a dropdown combo box that will display available vehicles from the vehicles table.  "										
		"D) AM Begin Mileage is the odometer reading from the vehicle selected at the time the driver starts the route.   I am a novice programmer and just want to stateMy intention as to how I want this to operate. I need a way to assign this route. at default vehicle I do not want it to be overly complicated, but I think if we just leave that one set as does default and we change it that new one becomes the default until it's changed again. If that makes sense. "										
		"E) And begin mileage should be. Addressed by looking at the route name and the bus number and that will set the next mileage event for that vehicle. So looking at it chronologically in date order. As an example, if June first the Truck Plaza was run by bus 17 in its begin mileage was 10,000 miles Then we assign that mileage to the vehicle in the vehicles. table. if you have questions about that, ask me and I can clarify.  It will also set. the beginning mileage for that route for that day. So also assigning that. odometer reading, if you will, for the truck plaza route in order to calculate how many miles were on that route. But if all of this can be done from the database, then I don't think we need to make a complex calculation here. You decide what's the best way to approach that. "										
		F)In the ending mileage column that. Completes the route for the AM portion. I'm just telling you all this for clear context on how this is currently done. 										
G		AM numbers is a manually entered field that will indicate how many students rode on that bus route that morning. 										
H		Am driver is intended to be a drop-down combo box and it will list all of the available drivers. From the drivers tab. 										
I		"Column I is the pm start mileage and it will complete the. Route for the day so the route consists of an AM portion and APM portion. So for that date in the date box. A complete route day would be the AM and the PM portion put together. but they are mirror images of the information that is contained and AM portion. that indicated for the PM portion. and those two together willComplete the route for that date. They are mirror images of each other. The AM is the first half, and the PM is the second half.  "										
												
		"That is all I want for the routes tab. If you have questions and need clarification, please do not hesitate to ask. Remember, I am a novice programmer. "										
