P											
	Primary Key	Bus Number	Model Year	Make	Model	VIN Number	Capacity	Last Inspection Date			
											
											
B	"Primary key is needed for the record, but assign it, but do not display it in the dynamic data grid view. "										
C	"Bus number is going to be a unique fleet number that we assign to a bus. This bus will never be deleted out of the database, but we. Do need to have a field. Where it is selected as active or inactive. If it is selected inactive, make it not possible for it to be selected in the other views drop down "										
D	Model gear will just be a four digit number manually input that identifies the model year of the bus or vehicle. 										
E	The vehicle manufacturer will be manually entered. 										
F	"The model number will be manually entered, and it can be an alphameric alphanumeric character. "										
G	"The number is also A, I think it's 17 or 18 digit alphanumeric. Number in all caps. "										
H	"Capacity will be manually entered, and it can range from one passenger to 100 passengers. "										
I	Last inspection date is going to be a date picker field and that indicates the last yearly inspection was completed. It will be used in future iteration. To allow the user to know when an upcoming inspection is going to be needed and plan for it. 										
											
											
